money-on-mobile.net 2018-05-09

# MoneyOnMobile

General

My Mobile Payments Limited, is registered at MoM House, Plot Not 61, Ramachandra Lane, Kanchpada, Malad (West), Mumbai - 400064, hereinafter referred to as MoneyOnMobile or we or the Company . The user hereby agrees that use of MoneyOnMobile's services or our interface implies your consent to the collection and use of your Information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy").

We take the privacy of our users seriously. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our users / Customers while providing a personalised and valuable service. 

Information Collected from You

In order for you to access certain areas of the Website, we may require you to provide us with certain information ("Personal Information"). Personal Information includes the following information: 

Your full name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, date of birth and bank or payment card details and any proof of your identity and/or address that we may request;

Details of any transactions user carries out through our Website / Mobile wallet using its  account and of the fulfilment of its requests;

Details of any bank account (including but not limited to, account holder, account name, account number, sort code, online banking PIN, Transaction Authentication Number "TAN" and password, available balance and transaction history of your bank account), ITR, TAX certificates or any other income documents as necessary by us;

Details of any credit, debit or other card used by you for transactions; 

Correspondence that you send us;

Surveys that you complete through the Website or based on our request;

Information collected through cookies. Please see Paragraph I (Cookies) of this Privacy Policy for more details;

Your IP address, log-in times, operating system and browser type; and

In order to fulfil our legal obligations to prevent fraud and money laundering, we will obtain information about you from third party agencies ("Third Party Information"), including your financial history, court judgements and bankruptcies, from credit reference and fraud prevention agencies when you open a MoneyOnMobile account and at any time when we feel it is necessary to prevent fraud and minimise our financial risks.

Personal Information and Third Party Information are collectively referred to as "Information".

Use and Storage of Information

We use your Information for the following purposes: 

To operate and administer your MoneyOnMobile account and to provide services that you have requested;

  To carry out your instructions to make and receive payments and undertake transactions using our services, including verifying that you have sufficient funds in your MoneyOnMobile wallet to make such payments;

To allow you to participate in interactive features of the Website;

To notify you about changes to our service(s);

To improve our internal customer training,

To comply with financial services regulations including retention of financial information and transactions;

For financial and identity checks, fraud prevention checks, anti-money laundering and credit checks;

For customer service, including answering questions and responding to feedback and complaints;

To enhance the security of our services;

To ensure that content on our Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer; and

To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you.

Disclosure of Information

Our site links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites. 

Cookies

"Cookies" are small computer files that are transferred to your computer's hard drive that contain information such as user ID, user preferences, lists of pages visited and activities conducted while browsing the Website. At your option, expense and responsibility, you may block cookies or delete cookies from your hard drive. However, by disabling cookies, you may not have access to the entire set of features of the Website.

The Company uses Cookies to customize your experience on our Website and to store your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Website.

We do not link the information stored in these Cookies directly to any of your Information you submit while on the Website.

No personal information will be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. 

Security Checks, Review and Releases

To maintain a high level of security, we reserves the right to conduct a security review at any time to validate your identity. To facilitate these security checks, you agree to provide such identification or other information or documentation as we, in our sole and unfettered discretion, deem necessary. If you fail to comply with any security request, we reserve the right to void your MoneyOnMobile account. You will be notified of such verification request by e-mail or telephone and your MoneyOnMobile account balances will be forfeited if you fail to provide us with such requested documentation and information within the time period reasonably specified by us.

Confidentiality and Security

The Company has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access. 

Public Information

Any information that you may reveal in a review posting or other online discussion or forum is intentionally open to the public and is not in any way private. You should think carefully before disclosing any personally identifiable information in any public forum. What you have written may be seen and/or collected by third parties and may be used by others in ways we are unable to control or predict.

Your Rights

You have a legal right to a copy of any Information about you held by us. You also have a right to correct any errors in that Information. As mentioned above, you have a right to request that we cease to use your Information for direct marketing purposes.

Restriction of Liability

The Company makes no claims, promises or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this Website and expressly disclaim liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this Website.

Warranties:

No warranty of any kind, implied, expressed or statutory, including but not limited to the warranties of non-infringement of third party rights, title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and freedom from computer virus, is given with respect to the contents of the Website or its hyperlinks to other internet resources.

Nothing in this Site or any materials shall be construed, implicitly or explicitly, as containing any investment recommendations. Accordingly, nothing in this Site, or in such materials, constitutes an offer of or an invitation by or on behalf of the Site to purchase or sell any shares or securities nor should it be considered as investment advice.

The contents of this website are under copyright and/or trademark of their original author(s) unless otherwise noted on the page itself.
